Hi,
>> greetings Rasheed. Can you hear me?
>> Yes, I can hear you.
>> Hey, good. Uh, I appreciate you taking
your time and doing this for us.
>> Oh, no problem. Thanks for having me on.
>> Yeah. Um, you were the top free agent
tackle and you signed um a team friendly
contract. You know, I realize every year
is a prove it year for NFL players, but
are you looking at this opportunity to
get a long-term commitment from either
the Panthers or another team uh next off
season? Um, I think it's just a great
opportunity just to play ball, you know.
Um, this is my fifth year in the NFL. A
lot of guys don't make it to their
second contract. So, I'm just happy to
be healthy and able to still do the
thing I love to do, which is play
football. So,
>> uh, the Panthers uh, uh, 16 to 13 win
uh, was big for the team at the time. uh
what was your perception of the Panthers
following that game and did it play a
role in deciding to to uh to come to
Charlotte?
>> Um well I think during that game I think
Carolina played some complimentary
football. Um you know it was a good
game. You know we were you know neck and
neck for a minute but I mean shoot
uh
I I don't know like I wouldn't say that
had you know something to do with me
picking Carolina. I just saw the
opportunity and you know I like where
the the program was headed and you know
I just wanted to be a part of it so
that's why I chose Carolina.
>> Right. Thanks. Uh good luck.
>> Thank you.
>> We'll go with David Newton followed by
Alex Zitlo.
>> Hey Rasheed. David Newton ESPN.com.
Appreciate you doing this today.
>> Yes sir.
>> Wanted to ask you uh back kind of
following up on that. Um you had not
resigned with Green Bay at the point
obviously. Uh, were they How How would
you gauge their interest? And then I'll
ask a followup to that.
>> Um, I mean, I really didn't have like I
let my agents take care of, you know,
all the talking to the teams and stuff.
I just really like, you know, I went
into free agency just with a mindset
like I was I was just happy to be
healthy. You know what I'm saying?
Health is well. So, you know, there'll
really be a better question for my agent
cuz I really didn't ask too many
questions. I was just waiting around and
you know waiting for the opportunity.
>> Well, part of that is cuz the Panthers
GM and others have said that they found
that the free agents like yourself, top
free agents, um seem to be easier to to
bring in and get a seat at the table
this year than they were a few years ago
when the team, you know, was was
struggling. Um, how much did that factor
in to you and what you saw in Carolina
versus maybe two years ago when they
were, you know, winning just a handful
of games?
>> Um, I mean, I feel like my job, you
know, as a left tackle is, you know, you
know, protect the quarterback, you know,
and I feel like, you know, with me
coming on to the team, I'm going to make
sure I do my job. And with the season
that Carolina had last year,
um, in addition to me, I feel like I'm
gonna make the team better.
>> Did they pretty much make you feel that
that that wouldn't be back this year or
wouldn't be back for most of the year or
what was the kind of the conversation
like?
>> Um, well, everyone, you know, was aware
of the situation.
I mean, so at the end of the day, like,
you know, my good friend Icky is down,
but you know, someone has to do the job.
And
um, you know, I think I'm a very good
football player and I think I'm going to
help this team get better.
>> Appreciate it.
>> Hey Rasheed, congrats on the contract
and welcome to Charlotte.
>> Thank you. Thank you.
>> Yeah. Um, I I wanted to follow up on
something you just said. Uh, you said my
good friend Icky. Uh, how well do you
know Icky and how did that relationship
start?
>> Um, well, we're we're in the same I
think we're in the same draft class.
Um,
I like I liked his game in college. Like
I like his college highlights, but um,
you know, we've crossed paths plenty of
times. You know, we both know who each
other are. So, you know, he's cool
people. You know, we've talked ever
since the signing. And you know, I I was
asking about Caroline, asking about the
team. Um, he's in high spirits, but
yeah, he's he's a really good guy and a
great person and an even better football
player.
>> What about his game did you like?
>> Well, no, on his college take when he
was at NC State, he was just played just
like he had one of the nastiest
highlights I ever seen as an offensive
lineman. So, you know, that's, you know,
that's that's kind of how I got on.
And you mentioned that um you and him
talked while you were making the
decision to ultimately come to Carolina.
I'm curious what did he say to you and
then ultimately why do you think the
Panthers were a good fit for you?
>> Well, I talked to him after I signed and
I was just asking him, you know, I
general questions like where should I
live at? Like um you know, how's
everything out there? Like how does he
like living out there and stuff like
that, you know, just stuff regular
questions like that.
>> Okay. But then from a Panthers fit
perspective, like why are the Panthers
ideal for you?
>> Um, I think the Panthers are ideal for
me. Well, honestly, I feel like, you
know, I'm the type of person any
situation I get, I'm going to make the
best of it. So, I feel like that's
already a positive. And, you know, I
feel like we have a really good
quarterback. Bryce Young have I have
some good um interior guard help with
me. And I feel like my job as a left
tackle, I'm going to bring that mindset
that, you know, I feel like the team
needs to get us over this over the edge.
>> Got it. Thanks, man.
>> Darren Gant,
>> how you doing, Rasheed? Wanted to ask
you, you just mentioned those guards.
How much do you know about Rob and Damen
and and even on the other side of Taylor
Motton, having a bunch of veterans on
that line with you?
>> Well, yeah. I've actually I've met
Taylor Motton um once. He's a pretty
cool guy. Um, you know, I like his game.
Um, Robert Hunt, I saw him catch a pass
a couple years ago. Um, that was
interesting, but I never met him him or
Damian, but I'm looking forward to
meeting those guys. But, uh, I'm just
ready to get in and start building, you
know, building the program, you know,
building the franchise up. And, you know
what I'm saying? Like the last
three out of the four seasons I was at
Green Bay, we went to the playoffs. So,
you know, I I think I know what it takes
to, you know, make it through the
playoffs and winning the playoffs. And,
you know, with the group of guys that we
have and and what the team is building,
I feel like, I mean, we have a shot.
>> Yeah. What What kind of things are you
focused on coming in just in terms of
getting to know Rob, Damian, Teemo, and
those guys?
>> Um, I'm I'm excited to just working with
them, you know?
Like I mean I feel like offensive line
is just you know it's all it is is five
guys with the same mindset. So you know
I definitely want to get in you know you
know break bread with the guys you know
get to know them and work with them you
know so we can all start playing like as
one cohesive unit
and all be on the same page.
>> Bashtai followed by David Newton.
>> Hi Rasheed. Uh welcome to Carolina. I
just want to ask you about Bryce Young.
What are your thoughts on Bryce Young?
And um how have you seen his game evolve
from afar as a player in the league?
>> Um well, I think Bryce Young, he's a
great player. I mean, he text me when I
signed. He said, "What's up?" He showed
some love. Um I've been watching some of
his highlights. I mean, he's just a good
player, great athlete. You know, I love
when my quarterback is athlete. You
know, that's always good. Um but I'm
I'mma protect him. I'mma do my job and
I'mma, you know, protect them.
>> It seems like a few of the guys reached
out to you. Is that is that standard or
is this kind of are you getting more
love than maybe you've gotten in the
past from these guys?
>> Well, yeah, I really appreciated um um a
couple of the guys reaching out to me.
It definitely made me feel like I was
entering into like, you know, a home
environment.
Uh
this this I mean this is my only team
I've ever played with on the Packers.
you know, when I came in, guys like
Aaron Jones and Kenny Clark greeted me
with open arms. So, it felt good to have
the same, you know, greetings and, you
know, for my new teammates to show me
some love.
>> Thanks,
>> David. You muted yourself.
>> David, you're still on mute.
>> Sorry about that. house. Uh, can you
tell me how you think the the gun charge
you had might have impacted free agency
for you?
>> Um, you know, I mean that's going to be
that's getting dismissed, but any
questions you have to um talk to my
lawyer?
>> Okay. Can you tell us your version of
what happened there?
>> No, I don't want to talk about that.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> Any more questions?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I have a couple. I'm sorry.
Sorry, I'm on my in my car and couldn't
figure out the raise hand thing.
Can Can you hear me?
>> Yeah, go ahead, Joe.
>> Okay. Hey, thanks, Kia. And uh thanks,
Rasheed. Um there was there was a report
that maybe some teams got scared off by
your medicals. Did Did one, were you
surprised that your market wasn't more
robust? I I know a lot of folks thought,
you know, you you were going to get a
multi-year deal for a lot of money. And
then secondly, you know, did did that
get back to you or your agent that you
know that folks had some medical
questions?
>> Um, I don't know. I mean, like I said, I
was just sitting around waiting. You
know, I did my four years at Green Bay
and I was just happy I got another
opportunity to play somewhere else. And
I feel like, you know, wherever I landed
at, they were getting a steal anyway
because what I bring to a team is, you
know, I bring intensity. Um the the I'm
a great teammate. I work hard and I go
hard for my teammates. So, you know what
I'm saying? I feel like, you know, by
the grace of God, I landed in Carolina.
I feel like it's going to be a great fit
and I'm just ready ready to do my job.
>> Completely understand that. That's uh
and you saying you feel like you're a
steal. And it kind of gets back to an
earlier question, but do you feel like
you go do your thing this year, then,
you know, you you get to do this free
agency thing uh again next year and and
hopefully uh it's more beneficial for
you?
>> Um I feel like it's it's always going to
be bene I'm I'm always going to be in a
you know, beneficial situation as long
as I'm healthy because I'm always going
to do what I'm supposed to do and I'm a
good football player.